# TRENTON MARKS

## FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Denver, CO (989) 494-3575 TRENTMARKS111@GMAIL.COM

### **PROFILE**

I am a full-stack web developer with a heavy entrepreneurial mindset. As I have gained more and more work experience, I have become intrigued at the essential role that software plays in the success and growth of each industry. Since I have first trained to understand basic business principles and the concepts behind driving consumers, I have a uniquely creative approach in the way that I develop software. I am a self sufficient individual that has a clear understanding of the ultimate end-game of each company that I help in its advancement.

## **SKILLS**

Ajax

• AngularJS

Bootstrap

CSS

Express.js

GitHub

Heroku

• HTML

JavaScript

Jquery

• Node.js

• Ruby

• Ruby on Rails

SQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT FELLOW

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | FEB 2018 - PRESENT

I participated in a full-time immersive web development course, completing in-class projects and personal projects focused on real-world application of web development principles tools and best practices. I also developed a portfolio of individually and collaboratively focused in-class projects.

#### SALES PROFESSIONAL

WIRELESS ZONE PREMIUM RETAILER | DEC 2015 - JUL 2018

This position has allowed me to develop sales skills like connecting, developing report, and closing. It has also allowed me to grow my abilities in sales calls, follow ups, appointment setting, and other customer relationship management. This job is strictly performance based which is what draws me to this job the most.

## **EDUCATION**

**UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN – Flint, MI | 2013 - 2015**